We at Fragment Media Group created this privacy policy because we know that you care about how information you provide to us is used and shared. 

This privacy policy relates to the information collection and use practices of The Daily Dot, Phire, and Nautilus in connection with our websites located at:

By visiting our site(s), you are agreeing to the terms of this policy and terms of use. 

Topics:

* Information we collect
* How we use your information
* How we protect your information
* How to opt out
* Links/other websites
* Children
* Changes to this privacy policy
* How to contact us

**Information we collect**
--------------------------

Personal information: We collect readers’ email addresses with their consent. We collect this information by using a pop-up on various pages. You can opt-out of entering your email and still enjoy the site.

Usage information – website: Like most websites, we use automatic data collection technology when you visit our site to record information that identifies your computer, to track your use of the site, and to collect certain basic information about you and your reading habits. This information includes information about your operating system, your IP addresses, your browser type and language, referring and exit pages and URLs, keywords, date and time, amount of time spent on particular pages, what sections of a website you visit, and similar information concerning your use of the site, including information about your sharing habits and patterns.

We collect usage information by using cookies and pixel tags (also called web beacons or clear gifs). Cookies are small packets of data that a website stores on your computer’s hard drive so that your computer will “remember” information about your visit. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of website users. You can reject cookies by following the directions provided in your browser’s help section. If you reject cookies, you may still visit the site, but you may have a less customizable experience.

For non-E.U. readers: Automatic data collection may be performed on our behalf by our service providers. We may also allow third-party companies that are presenting advertisements on the site to set and access their own cookies. Such third-party cookies are not governed by this privacy policy, but by the privacy policies of such third party.

Our properties may feature Nielsen proprietary measurement software, which will allow you to contribute to market research, such as Nielsen TV Ratings. To learn more about the information that Nielsen software may collect and your choices with regard to it, please see the Nielsen Digital Measurement privacy policy at [http://www.nielsen.com/digitalprivacy](http://www.nielsen.com/digitalprivacy).

We also work with advertisers that support the NAI. The NAI (Network Advertising Initiative) is a cooperative group of ad serving providers. The NAI has developed a set of privacy principles to which its members adhere. The NAI is committed to provide consumers with clear explanations of Internet advertising practices and how they affect you and the Internet generally. For more information about the NAI, third-party ad servers generally, and the opt-out opportunities available through the NAI, visit [optout.networkadvertising.org](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/).

Usage information – emails: When you view an email sent by us, we collect information regarding your device used to view the email such as: device operating system and web browser type and version. Emails sent include page tags (also known as web beacons) that provide us with additional information on your email activity (for example, when you open an email, click on a link, or share the email). The tracking of this information is the default behavior for all email participants. If you would like to turn off this tracking, see the _How to Opt Out_ section below.

**How we use your information**
-------------------------------

We may use your personal and usage information in a manner that is consistent with this policy and the context of our relationship with you. 

We will use emails collected on this site for the following purposes:

* To respond to your requests 
* To contact you about changes to this site 
* To send you notices (for example, in the form of emails and newsletters)

We may also use your usage information to:

* Improve our site and newsletters, and
* Enable us to customize your user experience through content and ads 

We may disclose to third parties aggregate data regarding user behavior as a measure of interest in, and use of, our site, such as overall patterns or demographic reports that do not describe or identify any individual user.

When you use our website, we share information that we collect from you, such as your email (if available, in hashed form), IP address, or information about your browser or operating system, with our identity partners/service providers, including LiveRamp Inc. LiveRamp returns an online identification code that we may store in our first-party cookie for our use in online, in-app, and cross-channel advertising and it may be shared with advertising companies to enable interest-based and targeted advertising. To opt out of this use, please click here ([https://liveramp.com/opt\_out/](https://liveramp.com/opt_out/))

We, like many businesses, sometimes hire other companies to perform certain business-related functions. Examples include maintaining databases, hosting services, and processing payments. When we employ another company to perform a function of this nature, we provide them with the information that they need to perform their specific function. We require such third parties to maintain the confidentiality of such information and use such information only as necessary to provide us with designated services. 

We may disclose user information to government authorities, and to other third parties when compelled to do so by government authorities, at our discretion, or otherwise as required by law, including but not limited to in response to court orders and subpoenas. We also may disclose user information when we have reason to believe that someone is or may be causing injury to or interference with our rights or property, other users of the site, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.

**How We Protect Your Information**
-----------------------------------

We take commercially reasonable steps to protect the personal information and the usage information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. Please understand, however, that no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our databases, nor can we guarantee that the information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to and from us over the internet.

### **How to Opt Out**

If you wish to stop receiving emails, you may also choose to unsubscribe from our emails by following the instructions in the bottom of the email. If you would like to opt out of email tracking or request the information we store about you, please contact us using the information below.

As mentioned above, if you want to opt out of providing usage information, you can reject cookies by following the directions provided in your browser’s help section.

### **Links/other websites**

The site contains content, services, advertising, and other materials that link to websites operated by third parties. We have no control over those other sites, and this privacy policy does not apply to them.

### **Children**

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If you are under 13, please do not give us any personal information. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s internet usage and to help enforce our policy by instructing their children to never provide personal information without permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided personal information to us, please contact us, and we will delete that information.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**
----------------------------------

We review and update this policy as needed, and we will place any updates on this page. This policy was last updated on the date at the bottom of this page. By accessing the site after we make any such changes to this privacy policy, you are deemed to have accepted such changes. Please refer back to this privacy policy on a regular basis.

**How to Contact Us**
---------------------

If you would like to turn off email tracking, please email us at [\[email protected\]](https://fragmnt.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)   with “EMAIL TRACKING” in the subject line.

If you have questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please email us at [\[email protected\]](https://fragmnt.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) with “PRIVACY POLICY” in the subject line, or mail us at the following address:

Fragment Media Group LLC

3112 Windsor Road, Suite A391

Austin, TX 78703

_Last updated: April 25, 2022_

#### Get Updates

Subscribe by Email

Submit your email to get Fragment Media news updates in your inbox.

First Name 

Last Name 

Email \* 

If you are human, leave this field blank. 

Subscribe

Made with 🎸 in Austin, Texas.

Fragment is a registered benefit company.
